wheelers.co 2018-02-20

# Privacy Policy - Wheelers Books

Wheelers has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This document discloses our information gathering and usage practices. For additional information about Wheelers Books, please review our Terms of Use.

## Use of your information

Wheelers Books does not sell or rent your personal identification to third parties. We release account and other personal information only when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply to our terms and conditions; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Wheelers Books, our users, or others.

## Email

It is the policy of Wheelers Books to only send our members email they elect to receive, in addition to customary business communications (payment confirmations, etc.). Further, it is our policy to immediately remove any member from any mailing list upon the member's request. In addition, for those who elect to receive it Wheelers Book will send a monthly newsletter to members. Newsletters will contain clear and obvious instructions for how the member can remove himself or herself from that mailing list should they want to. We also use email as a means of receiving feedback from our members, and we encourage you to email us with your questions or comments.

## Credit Card Security

We work diligently to protect the security of your personal information, including credit card information.

We protect your credit card information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. When paying by credit card, you can choose to "save this card for next time". If you choose this option, your credit card details are encrypted and securely stored by Direct Payment Solutions (DPS). Review their Privacy Policy (PDF document). Your credit card details are not held by Wheelers Books and can not be accessed by Wheelers Books staff.

## Membership Removal

If you wish to have your registration removed from our directory for any reason, simply send us an email requesting to be removed.

If you have any questions about our privacy policies or any other matter, please contact us.
